affiliated-business.com 2007-03-21

# Privacy Policy

|  |  |  |  |   
---  
| 

## Affiliated-Business.com Privacy Policy

Affiliated-Business.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period." 

**How we gather information from users**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, Affiliated-Business.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences. 

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone. 

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Affiliated-Business.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by Affiliated-Business.com and other topics we think you might find of interest. 

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Affiliated-Business.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases. 

**Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**

Affiliated-Business.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Affiliated-Business.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Affiliated-Business.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Affiliated-Business.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. 

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Affiliated-Business.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. 

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Affiliated-Business.com and this policy. 

**Children**

Affiliated-Business.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Affiliated-Business.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below. 

**Contacting Us**

We can be reached by contacting: 

Affiliated-Business.com

**Changes to this Policy**

Affiliated-Business.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected. 

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Ohio law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Delaware, Ohio. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us. 

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Delaware, Ohio, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so. 

Affiliated-Business.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Ohio. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

|   
| 

##  Your Privacy 

### We respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to our website (Affiliated-Business.com) need to be in control of their personal information.

We respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to our website (Affiliated-Business.com) need to be in control of their personal information. We also want to present information on Affiliated-Business.com that is tailored to the needs of our visitors. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information when you visit certain areas of our site, download software, subscribe to a newsletter or join chat/forums. We will use this information to ensure the content, services, and advertising that we provide are tailored to your current and future needs. If you provide Affiliated-Business.com with your mailing address or telephone number, Affiliated-Business.com and its partners may use this information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and new services. If you provide your e-mail address, Affiliated-Business.com may contact you via e-mail as well. If you do not want Affiliated-Business.com, our alliance partners, or selected third parties to contact you, you may opt out when you provide personal information or contact Affiliated-Business.com directly. For instructions, please click on "Contact" above. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you will still be granted to most of Affiliated-Business.com's Web sites. However, you will not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a server. They contain only information that users volunteer, and they cannot infiltrate a user's hard drive and sneak away with personal information. The simple function of a cookie is to help the user save time and allow personalization of webpages. 

**How a Cookie Helps Affiliated-Business.com**

Cookies allows us to be more efficient. We can learn what information is important to our visitors, and what isn't. We can remove content that are not important to you and focus our efforts on things that matter to you. 

You can always disable cookies by "turning off cookies" within your browser. Please consult your browser manuals for more details. 

**Use of Information**

Any information you provide to Affiliated-Business.com over this website is maintained and accessible only by Affiliated-Business.com and its alliance partners. Affiliated-Business.com obtains this information to broadcast important information such as product updates and special offers. Affiliated-Business.com will not disclose any information about any individual user to entities outside of those partners except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process. 

**Third-party web sites**

The Affiliated-Business.com and worldwide mirror sites contains links to third-party web sites. The linked sites are not under the control of Affiliated-Business.com, and Affiliated-Business.com is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. Affiliated-Business.com is providing these links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked site by Affiliated-Business.com. 

**Sharing of Information**

The individually identifiable information that you provide will be used extensively within the Affiliated-Business.com website to provide a personalized experience for you. Affiliated-Business.com's use of the information submitted by you may be altered to better suit visitors. 

__

I am a strong believer in the rights to privacy of people who use the Internet.  At the Affiliated-Business.com site, I will not collect any personally identifiable information from visitors, except with their permission (explicit or implied) as a result of such visitor-initiated actions as signing up for a newsletter, mail list, or "tell-a-friend.". E-mail addresses supplied in those circumstances may be used to provide visitors with e-mailings about this site and related topics. 

Visitors should be aware that this site contains many third-party links to and from other sites on the Internet. Many of these connections use cookies and other means to track the progress of people in this site - such as the tracking service provided by Hitbox.com to measure traffic at this site.  Some links to other sites will involve tracking for affiliate-accounting & traffic-monitoring purposes and will therefore track a visitor's movement to, and at, other sites.  All third party links and connections are governed by the individual  privacy policies of those other sites. 

If you believe that you have received "spam" or other unsolicited communications as a result of visiting Affiliated-Business.com, [**please contact me**](mailto:danrusso@affiliated-business.com) to let me know so I can take any appropriate action to remedy the situation. 

With best regards - Daniel Russo

|   
|  |  |   
---  
WEB BUSINESS RESOURCES  
---  
  
Become A Super Affiliate Overnight! Adword Equalizer Finds The Most Profitable Search Terms And Products For You!  
  
* * *

---  
  
"I struggled to achieve top positions in the search engines, for several keywords with slow but steady progress. When I purchased **SEO Elite** I have seen immediate results. I have achieved top placement for a number of competitive keywords that include two and three word phrases. I am very pleased and appreciative of **SEO Elite** team's hard work, brilliance, and generosity."  

* * *

---  
  
Just one simple Google AdWords campaign, which takes less than 30 minutes a week, earns me thousands per month. And in Google Adwords I show you exactly how I did it, and how you can too.  
  
* * *

* * *
